<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CoLiDo</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_diy">DIY</string>
    <string name="title_activity_choose_printer">CoLiDo</string>
    <string name="diy_button_description">DIY</string>
    <string name="compact_button_description">Compact</string>
    <string name="two_plus_button_description">2 Plus</string>
    <string name="m2020_button_description">M2020</string>
    <string name="x3045_button_description">X3045</string>
    <string name="title_activity_load_manual">LoadManual</string>
    <string name="title_activity_show_manual">ShowManual</string>
    <string name="drawer_open">Open Navigation Drawer</string>
    <string name="drawer_close">Close Navigation Drawer</string>
    <string name="bed_calibration_title">Bed calibration for CoLiDo Compact</string>
    <string name="clogged_nozzle_title">Fixing a clogged nozzle</string>
    <string name="print_head_removal_title">Replacing the print head</string>
    <string name="nozzle_replacement_title">Replacing the nozzle unit</string>
    <string name="load_file_title">Loading a File</string>
    <string name="slice_file_title">Slicing a File</string>
    <string name="object_controls_title">Using Object Placement Controls</string>
    <string name="filament_types_title">Different Filament Types</string>
    <string name="inserting_filament_title">Inserting Filament</string>
    <string name="recommended_temps_title">Recommended Temperatures</string>
    <string name="sd_print_title">Using an SD card without an LCD screen</string>

    <string name="bed_calibration">1.\tClick the Z home button to raise the bed into the printing position.\n\n2.\tOnce the bed has been raised, position
    the printer head over the back right wing nut.\n\n3.\tUse the test sheet that came with the printer and place it between the nozzle and the
    platform.\n\n4.\tTurn the wing nut until the nozzle is just touching the test sheet. The test sheet should just be able to slide out.\n\n
        5.\tMove the print head over to the back left wing nut and then the front wing nut and repeat steps 3 and 4.</string>

    <string name="clogged_nozzle">Heat the extruder up to 240c and push through some filament, this may un-clog the nozzle.\n\nWhile the extruder is at temperature for the filament which you are using, take a length of filament and load it into
    the extruder.\n\nPush the filament through the extruder so that it starts coming out of the nozzle (it might not if you have a full clog)\n\nCool the nozzle down to around 100c and keep pushing the filament through until no more will come out of the nozzle.\n\nOnce the nozzle has cooled to this
    temperature try to pull the filament out of the extruder. If the filament does not pull out without snapping, heat the extruder up to printing temperature
    and keep pulling the filament until it pops out of the extruder.\n\nYou should see some black bits and dirt on the end of the filament. Cut off the end
    and repeat until the filament is clean.</string>

    <string name="print_head_removal">1.\tRemove the cover to the board which the fan, extruder, and nozzle plug in.\n\n2.\tRemove the plugs from the board for the fan, nozzle, and extruder motors. \n\n3.\tTo remove the whole print head from the carriage unscrew the screws underneath the carriage using the
    supplied allen key.\n\n4.\tPlace the new head where the old one was and use the allen key to screw the print head to the frame.
    \n\n5.\tPlug all of the wires back in to the board and screw on the cover.\n\n6.\tIt is best to recalibrate the build plate once you have replaced the print head as the
    nozzle position will most likely have changed.</string>

    <string name="nozzle_removal">1.\tRemove the cover to the board where the nozzle heating wire (double red) and thermistor wire (double white) plug in to and unplug these wires.
    \n\n2.\tUse the supplied allen key to remove the 2 screws at the front of the fan. Be careful not to lose any of the parts when removing the screws.\n\n3.\tUnscrew the small
    white plastic piece at the top of the nozzle. You may need some pliers to loosen the piece.\n\n4.\tLoosen the small black grub screw at the front of the metal block using the long thin allen key.
    Try not to remove the screw as it is easy to lose.\n\n5.\tThe nozzle should push out from the metal block if the screws are lose enough and all the plugs have been removed.
    \n\n6.\tPlace the new nozzle in the metal block, plug in the wires, and screw everything back in.\n\n7.\tIt is best to recalibrate the build plate once you have replaced a nozzle as the
    position will probably have changed.</string>

    <string name="recommended_temps"><b>PLA nozzle:</b> 190&#8211;210c\t <b>PLA bed:</b> 60&#8211;70c\n\n<b>ABS nozzle:</b>240c\t <b>ABS bed:</b> 110c\n\n<b>PA(Nylon) nozzle:</b> 240&#8211;260c
    \t<b>PA(Nylon) bed:</b> 80&#8211;100c\n\n<b>PC+ nozzle:</b> 240&#8211;260c\t<b>PC+ bed:</b> 110&#8211;120c</string>

    <string name="inserting_filament">1.\t Remove the filament spool from its packaging. Keep hold of the silica get as it can be useful for filament
    storage.\n\n2.\t Mount the filament spool onto the spool holder so that the filament rotates in a counter clockwise direction.\n\n3.\t
     Gently pull the filament from the spool. Cut the filament flat for easy installation.\n\n4.\t Insert the filament into the tube until it comes
    out of the other end of the tube.\n\n5.\t Push down on the printer head arm and insert the filament into the hole at the top of the printer head.
    Push the filament until it reaches the end of the nozzle, then release the printer head arm.\n\nPlease note: when changing filament from a hotter melting
    point to a lower one, use the hotter melting point to flush out the old filament.</string>

    <string name="load_file">To print a custom file, you will need a 3D design in either .stl or .obj file format. You can download these files
    from websites such as www.MyMiniFactory.com or design your own using CAD or other 3D design software.\n\nTo load the file into Repetier Host click the
    load button located in the top left. Navigate through your files to find the correct .stl or .obj file and click open to load the file.\n\nMultiple
    files can be loaded onto the build plate at once.</string>

    <string name="slice_file">For your .stl or .obj file to be ready for 3D printing it needs to be "sliced" first. Slicing converts the design file into individual
    layers and each layer has a set of commands to tell the 3D printer what to do.\n\nTo slice a file, first make sure that you have the correct
    settings for the printer you are using. These settings can vary depending on the printer model, quality and printing temperatures.\n\nOnce you
    have checked the slicing settings click the slice button and a progress bar will appear.\n\nWhen the slicing has finished you can either print the
    file on a connected printer or save the newly created gcode file so it can be printing using an SD card or saved for later.\n\nPlease note: If you are
    using a printer without a heated bed use only Slic3r and not CuraEngine.</string>

    <string name="object_controls"><b>Export:</b> If you have loaded multiple files into the software you can use this button to export them out as one file.
    \n\n<b>Add Object:</b> This has the same function as the load button.\n\n<b>Copy Object(s):</b> If you wish to copy an object without loading it in multiple times you
    can click this button and select the number of copies.\n\n<b>Auto-Position:</b> This will automatically position the selected object in the centre of the
    build plate.\n\n<b>Centre Object:</b> Centres the selected object relative to the size of the bed.\n\n<b>Scale Object:</b> This will increase or decrease the size
    in any or the entire xyz axis. To scale uniformly (in all axis) keep the padlock locked and enter a value into the X axis box. To scale non-uniformly
    unlock the padlock and you will be able to enter individual values for all axis.\n\n<b>Rotate Object:</b> A value can be entered into one of the xyz axis
    to rotate in the chosen axis by that value, from 0-360 degrees.</string>

    <string name="different_filament"><b>ABS:</b> Its strength, flexibility, machinability, and higher temperature resistance make it often a preferred
    plastic for engineers, and professional applications. The hot plastic smell deters some as does the plastics petroleum based origin. The additional
    requirement of a heated bed means that some printers are incapable of reliably printing ABS. \n\n<b>PLA:</b> The wide range of available colours and translucencents
    and glossy feel often attract those who print for display or small household users. Many appreciate the plant based origins and prefer the semi-sweet smell
    over ABS. When properly cooled, PLA seems to have higher maximum printing speeds, lower layer heights, and sharper printed corners. Combining this with low
    warping on parts make it a popular plastic for home printers, hobbyists, and schools.</string>

    <string name="sd_print">Some of our printers do not have an LCD screen and need to be controlled by a computer through a USB cable. However they
    still have an SD card slot so can be used without connecting to a computer.\n\nSlice a file with the correct settings for the printer you will
    be printing from.\n\nInstead of clicking print, click "save for SD print" and save the file onto an SD card. When naming the file, "auto0.g" must
    be used otherwise nothing will happen when you turn on the printer.\n\nInsert the SD card into the SD card slot on the printer. Make sure the back
    of the SD card is facing up.\n\nMake sure the printer is not connected to a computer and turn it on. The file should start to print automatically.</string>

    <string name="u_extrusion">Under extrusion occurs when there is not enough material being extruded out of the nozzle and so incomplete layers
    appear in the printed object. Sometimes this problem is caused by the filament being used. Check that the filament is not being printed at too
    low or too high temperatures as it may not be able to flow evenly through the nozzle if this is the case. Temperatures for each filament can be seen
    in the recommended temperatures section of tips and tricks.\n\nIf the filament feeder makes a ticking sound then the problem is that the filament
    is not moving through properly. The extruder gears will be grinding the filament and there may not be enough grip to move the filament through.
    Check the spool for any tangles and reload the filament into the extruder, cutting off the end which has been grinding. If the filament is still grinding
    then the problem may be a clogged nozzle. See the fixing a clogged nozzle section of tips and tricks.</string>

    <string name="o_extrusion">If there is too much filament being extruded then it can cause the print to look messy. Most of the time the
    extrusion multiplier will need to be lowered. This can be changed in the filament settings of slicer configuration. Start by decreasing the
    multiplier by 0.5 and then continue to decrease until the over extrusion has stopped.</string>

    <string name="stringing">Stringing occurs when filament oozes out from the nozzle whilst the print head is in transit. This is usually caused by
    printing at too high temperatures or not enough filament retraction.\n\nTo lower the temperatures go into the printer setting in Repetier-Host
    and in the printer tab change the default extruder temperature. At first decrease the temperature by 5 degrees and then start a test print to see
    if the stringing has been reduced. Keep changing the temperature until the best results are achieved. Do not go outside the recommended printing
    temperature for the filament you are using.\n\n To increase the retraction the slicer settings will need to be changed. This can be done by going into
    the slicer configuration settings from the slicer tab in Repetier-Host and finding where retraction settings are located, usually under extruder or
    extrusion settings. From here the retraction distance and speed can be increased, amongst other settings. As with the temperature, increase the distance
    and speed by small increments and print a test after each settings change. You should start to see less stringing but beware, if you have too much
    retraction it can cause under extrusion after the retract as the filament will take longer to reach the end of the nozzle.\n\nAnother small change that
    can be made is increasing the print head travel speed. Increasing this to a value around 150mm/s will give the filament less time to ooze out from
    the nozzle before it starts printing again</string>

    <string name="bed_adhesion">If a print is not sticking to the bed at the start of a print then it can cause issues for the rest of the print job.
    If the printer being used has a heated bed look at the recommended bed temperatures for the filament being used.\n\nThe most common cause of this
    problem is the build plate not being calibrated correctly. Either use the built in calibration function of our range of 3D printers or refer to the bed
    calibration section in tips and tricks. Ideally the nozzle should just be squashing the filament against the build plate rather than dropping filament
    onto it.\n\nIf the filament is being extruded thin and wispy then the problem is with the nozzle which could be clogged. See the fixing a clogged nozzle
    section in tips and tricks to help.</string>

    <string name="warping">Warping occurs when part of a print, usually an edge or corner, contracts while cooling and shrinks causing the part to lift
    up from the build plate. There are many ways to prevent warping.\n\nThe build plate could be causing the part to warp. Check the temperatures
    and calibration of the build plate. The temperatures can be found in the recommended temperatures section of tip and tricks and for calibration see
    the calibration section or use the 3D printers built in calibration function. A thin layer of glue can also be applied to the build plate to help
    the part adhere.\n\nSome slicer settings can also be changed to help. To access these click the configuration button in the slicer tab of Repetier-Host
    If there is not already a brim when the model has been sliced, you can add one by setting brim width to anything other than 0mm. If brim width is
    set to 6mm then a single layer will be printed around the object 6mm wide. A raft can also be added by increasing the raft layers. A raft adds a grid
    between the build plate and the model causing heat to be distributed equally.A decrease in first layer speed and an increase in first layer thickness
    can also stop filament catching the nozzle and being dragged around.</string>

    <string name="overheating">Some prints will suffer from overhanging edges not being printed properly. In most cases this can be solved by having a fan
    face the printer whilst it is printing. This help to cool down each layer a prevents them from drooping over the previous one. Be careful not to set
    the fan too powerful as this could cause the print to move on the build plate.\n\nIf the fan does not solve the problem then supports may need to
    be printed under the overhangs. Supports can be set in the configuration settings of the slicer and can be changed to cover more or less of the model by
    changing the overhang threshold.</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_tips_tricks">TipsTricks</string>
    <string name="section_format">Hello World from section: %1$d</string>
    <string name="title_activity_show_tips">ShowTips</string>
    <string name="title_activity_troubleshooting">Troubleshooting</string>
    <string name="title_activity_show_troubleshooting">ShowTroubleshooting</string>
    <string name="title_activity_contact_us">ContactUs</string>
</resources>
