<resources>
    <string name="app_name">My Application</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_diy">DIY</string>
    <string name="title_activity_choose_printer">CoLiDo</string>
    <string name="diy_button_description">DIY</string>
    <string name="compact_button_description">Compact</string>
    <string name="two_plus_button_description">2 Plus</string>
    <string name="m2020_button_description">M2020</string>
    <string name="x3045_button_description">X3045</string>
    <string name="title_activity_load_manual">LoadManual</string>
    <string name="title_activity_show_manual">ShowManual</string>
    <string name="drawer_open">Open Navigation Drawer</string>
    <string name="drawer_close">Close Navigation Drawer</string>
    
    <string name="bed_calibration">1.\tClick the Z home button to raise the bed into the printing position.\n\n2.\tOnce the bed has been raised, position
    the printer head over the back right wing nut.\n\n3.\tUse the test sheet that came with the printer and place it between the nozzle and the
    platform.\n\n4.\tTurn the wing nut until the nozzle is just touching the test sheet. The test sheet should just be able to slide out.\n\n
        5.\tMove the print head over to the back left wing nut and then the front wing nut and repeat steps 3 and 4.</string>

    <string name="clogged_nozzle">Heat the extruder up to 240c and push through some filament, this may un-clog the nozzle.\n\nWhile the extruder is at temperature for the filament which you are using, take a length of filament and load it into
    the extruder.\n\nPush the filament through the extruder so that it starts coming out of the nozzle (it might not if you have a full clog)\n\n
    Cool the nozzle down to around 100c and keep pushing the filment through until no more will come out of the nozzle.\n\n Once the nozzle has cooled to this
    temperature try to pull the filament out of the extruder. If the filament doesn not pull out without snapping, heat the extruder up to printing temperature
    and keep pulling the filament until it pops out of the extruder.\n\nYou should see some black bits and dirt on the end of the filament. Cut off the end
    and repeat until the filament is clean.</string>

    <string name="print_head_removal">1.\tUse the supplied allen key to remove the 2 screws at the front of the fan. Be careful when removing them
    not to loose any of the parts.\n\n2.\tUse the long, thin allen key to unscrew the small black grub screw facing the front of the printer. Try not to remove the
    grub screw completely to avoid losing it.\n\n3.\tTo remove the whole print head from the carriage unscrew the screws underneath the carriage using the
    supplied allen key.</string>

    <string name="recommended_temps"> PLA nozzle 190-210c\tPLA bed: 60-70c\n\nABS nozzle:240c\tABS bed: 110c\n\nPA(Nylon) nozzle: 240-260c
    \tPA(Nylon) bed: 80-100c\n\nPC+ nozzle: 240-260c\tPC+bed: 110-120c</string>

    <string name="inserting_filament"> 1.\t Remove the filament spool from its packaging. Keep hold of the silica get as it can be useful for filament
    storage.\n\n2.\t Mount the filament spool onto the spool holder so that the filament rotates in a counter clockwise direction.\n\n3.\t
     Gently pull the filament from the spool. Cut the filament flat for easy installation.\n\n4.\t Insert the filament into the tube until it comes
    out of the other end of the tube.\n\n5.\t Push down on the printer head arm and insert the filament into the hole at the top of the printer head.
    Push the filament until it reaches the end of the nozzle, then release the printer head arm.\n\nPlease note: when changing filament from a hotter melting
    point to a lower one, use the hotter melting point to flush out the old filament.</string>

    <string name="load_file"> To print a custom file, you will need a 3D design in either .stl or .obj file format. You can download these files
    from websites such as www.MyMiniFactory.com or design your own using CAD or other 3D design software.\n\nTo load the file into Repetier Host click the
    load button located in the top left. Navigate through your files to find the correct .stl or .obj file and click open to load the file.\n\nMultiple
    files can be loaded onto the build plate at once.</string>

    <string name="slice_file"> For you .stl or .obj file to be ready for 3D printing it needs to be "sliced" first. Slicing converts the design file into individual
    layers and each layer has a set of commands to tell the 3D printer what to do.\n\nTo slice a file, first make sure that you have the correct
    settings for the printer you are using. These settings can vary depending on the printer model, quality and printing temperatures.\n\nOnce you
    have checked the slicing settings click the slice button and a progress bar will appear.\n\nWhen the slicing has finished you can either print the
    file on a connected printer or save the newly created gcode file so it can be printing using an SD card or saved for later.\n\nPlease note: If you are
    using a printer without a heated bed use only Slic3r and not CuraEngine.</string>

    <string name="object_controls"> Export: If you have loaded multiple files into the software you can use this button tp export them out as one file.
    \n\nAdd Object: This has the same function as the load button.\n\nCopy Object(s): If you wish to copy an object without loading it in multiple times you
    can click this button and select the number of copies.\n\nAuto-Position: This will automatically position the selected object in the centre of the
    build plate.\n\nCentre Object Centres the selected object relative to the size of the bed.\n\nScale Object: This will increase or decrease the size
    in any or the entire xyz axis. To scale uniformly (in all axis) keep the padlock locked and enter a value into the X axis box. To scale non-uniformly
    unlock the padlock and you will be able to enter individual values for all axis.\n\nRotate Object: A value can be entered into one of the xyz axis
    to rotate in the chosen axis by that value, from 0-360 degrees.</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_tips_tricks">TipsTricks</string>
    <string name="section_format">Hello World from section: %1$d</string>
    <string name="title_activity_show_tips">ShowTips</string>
</resources>
